module.exports = [
  // {
  //   heading: 'Branch',
  //   question: 'Collect a deposit slip from your nearest FNB branch and have your teller stamp it for you. Question re the stamp.',
  //   answer: []
  // },
  {
    heading: 'Branch',
    question: 'What time does the Melrose Arch branch close on a Saturday? Please enter your answer in the format hh:mm.',
    answer: ['12:30'],
    order: 1
  },
  {
    heading: 'ATM',
    question: 'What is the telephone number you should call if your card is swallowed by an ATM? Hint, it starts with 087.',
    answer: ['0875759406'],
    order: 2
  },
  // {
  //   heading: 'ATM',
  //   question: 'How many language options are available to choose from on an ATM?',
  //   answer: ['12']
  // },
  // {
  //   heading: 'Banking App',
  //   question: 'The FNB Banking App can be downloaded for which Smartphones?',
  //   answer: ['apple', 'blackberry', 'android', 'windows mobile']
  // },
  {
    heading: 'Banking App',
    question: 'Can you apply for a loan on your Banking App? Please type y for yes and n for no.',
    answer: ['y'],
    order: 3
  },
  {
    heading: 'Online Banking',
    question: 'We take safety and security very seriously. What protection software do we use?',
    answer:['webroot secureanywhere'],
    order: 4
  },
  {
    heading: 'Online Banking',
    question: 'Calculate a home loan using our online bond calculator. If you purchase a home for R885 000.00 over 240 months at an interest rate of 9.25% (no initiation fee), what would your monthly repayment be? Please round off to two decimal places.',
    answer: ['8105.42'],
    order: 5
  },
  // {
  //   heading: 'Cellphone Banking'
  //   question: 'How many characters needed for a cellphone banking password?',
  //   answer: [7]
  // },
  // {
  //   heading: 'Cellphone Banking'
  //   question: 'What is the USSD code one needs to dial to recharge with prepaid airtime, electricity or data?',
  //   answer: [7]
  // },
  {
    heading: 'Switching',
    question: 'How many minutes does it take to switch to FNB?',
    answer: ['10'],
    order: 6
  }

]